Aaron Zomback Full Stack Engineer

Q Lyon, France ■ aaronzomback@protonmail.com **Q** https://www.github.com/aaronzomback

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaron-zomback/ ★ https://www.zomback.design

Profile

Versatile developer from a professional scientific research background with a strong portfolio of skills including analytical testing, creative problem solving, presentation, and communication.

Skills

Javascript | Typescript | NodeJS | Express | React | React Native | Ruby-on-Rails | GraphQL | MongoDB | Python PostgreSQL | Neo4j | RESTful APIs | Koa | Angular | Unit & Integration Testing | Apollo

Professional Experience

Frontend engineer 2021 – present

Foodprint.

Web app that connects eco-friendly food lovers, restaurants, and local food suppliers. Contributed to the frontend as part of a team of four. My responsibilities included:

- Implementing dynamic registration forms
- · Adding functionality to user profile pages
- · Creating a consistent & attractive design system

Tech Stack: React & Typescript

Quality Assurance Engineer 2021

ReadIt

A web app for people who enjoy reading offering the ability to search books and keep track of the books they want to read with the ability to rate them.

- Piloted quality assurance while conducting application testing (Jest) within a team 3 developers.
- Influenced improvements and optimisations on UX/UI, reliability and scalability.
- Refactored codebase into Typescript

Tech Stack: Jest/React testing library

Sr. Research Associate Scientist

2014 - 2019 | Brooklyn, NY

Calder Biosciences

Designed and conducted experiments to analyze potential vaccine candidates for HIV, RSV, & Influenza.

Projects

TimeSink 2021 – present

Full Stack Engineer

Next-gen cinema platform for supporting great filmmakers and connecting audiences. Part-time side project.

Tech Stack: Ruby-on-Rails & Javascript

Oku 2021

Full Stack Engineer

Mobile app where creators can write, share, submit, view featured illustrated-haiku galleries, and collect others' haikus as part of a dynamic and creative social network.

- Designed data schema
- Created graphql queries & mutations
- Connected the data from backend to front end through graphl/apollo api
- Implemented a responsive and user-friendly frontend

Tech Stack: GraphQL/Apollo API, React Native, Node/Express, and Neo4js graph database.

Education

Computer Science (M.S.) | Georgia Institute of Technology 2021 - present | Atlanta Software Engineering | Codeworks 2021 | Remote

Biochemistry (B.S.) | University of Washington

2014 | Seattle

Languages

English | French (Currently on A2/B1 track) | Spanish (Limited working proficiency)